{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5154","name":"Grey Ghost Detroit","address":"47 E Watson St","owner":"John Vermiglio","licenseNumber":"203393","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42800","inspectionDate":"2018-07-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135Â° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"ICE BIN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate."}]},{"inspectionid":"40864","inspectionDate":"2017-11-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"for raw or undercooked food(s)/ingredient(s) eggs","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MENU(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"38553","inspectionDate":"2017-04-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"for raw or undercooked food(s)/ingredient(s)","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MENU(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-203.12","violationDescription":"SHELLSTOCK tags shall remain attached to the container in which the shellstock are received until the container is empty and tags shall be retained for 90 days after the container is empty.  Retained tags shall be kept in chronological order and correlated to the date when shellstock are harvested. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Shellstock","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Identification","subProblem":"Tag(s) not retained for 90 days","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Retain on file."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."}]},{"inspectionid":"37077","inspectionDate":"2016-09-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"MENU(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS (BAR)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5154"}}